Sanjay Singh Chauhan

PERMANENT ADDRESS

35-I, Dr. Singha colony, Abu -Road, Mount Abu

CURRENT ADDRESS

Behind Shri Nath hospital, New navratan complex, Udaipur

PHONE

9653770302 9414993737(WhatsApp)

EMAIL

Kundan3333@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A trustworthy, dependable, responsible employee with 2 years of experience providing ongoing support to a successful company within the technology industry. Experience in customer service and events. Dedicated professional with a keen ability to maximize both time and business efficiencies. Well-organized with in-depth technical knowledge and keen attention to detail.

EXPERIENCE

Logic Circle, *Noida, Uttar Pradesh- content and blog writer* AUG 2020 - NOV 2020

- Academic writing.
- Blog writing.
- Proofreading, and research.

Cognus Technology, Udaipur, Rajasthan- Team leader

NOV 2017 - OCT 2019

- Keep records of assignments and produce detailed work reports.
- Monitor production rates, and plan rework processes to improve production.
- Allotment of work to team members.
- Use computers, audio-visual aids, and other equipment and materials to supplement presentations.
- Maintain daily worksheet on excel.

• Leave management.

Fusion Business Solutions, Udaipur Rajasthan - Associate

OCT 2016 - MARCH 2017

- Provide services to customers, such as order placement or account information.
- Conduct searches to find needed information, using such sources as the internet.
- Prepare and mail checks.

Fay's infotech bpo call center, Abu road, Rajasthan - Associate NOV 2012 - FEB 2013

EDUCATION

National Academy of Event Management, Jaipur Rajasthan - MBA, Event management & PR
JULY 2016

St Paul's college of science & management, Abu Road, Rajasthan - B.com, Commerce.

AUG 2013

St Anselm's School, Abu Road, Rajasthan

JUL 2010

SKILLS

- Team Working
- Quick learning
- MS Office
- Online Marketing
- Management